newsi18.com 2011-02-03

# Privacy >> Newsi18 | Breaking News And Latest Words From India

Thanks for visiting our web site at url www.newsi18.com (called as site hereafter). This privacy policy page tells you about how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this page before using the site or submitting any personal information to site. By using this site, you are accepting the practices that are solely described in this page. These practices may be altered, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. We highly encourage youto review the privacy policy whenever you visit this site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:** the privacy practices set forth in this page are for this site only; If you link to other web sites through this (third party sites/pages), please review the privacy policies described at those sites individually.

**Collection of Information  
**We collect personally identifiable information, like name, website addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mail subscription (by Feedburner) lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
**The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: info.newsi18(at)gmail(dot)com  
By Phone: +91 958 974 1068

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

Updated: 7th October 2010.
